<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TR</title>
    <link>http://ltratcliff.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 08:55:17 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://ltratcliff.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Media Backup</title>
      <link>http://ltratcliff.com/posts/media-backup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 08:55:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ltratcliff.com/posts/media-backup/</guid>
      <description>Backup Media From DVD to Filesystem  Get sector size and count of the DVD  sudo isosize -x /dev/sr0 Write the contents of the DVD to an ISO  sudo dd if=/dev/sr0 of=dvd.iso bs=2048 count=2131422 status=progress Mount the ISO and inspect the contents  sudo mount -o loop dvd.iso /mnt/iso ls /mnt/iso/VIDEO_TS/ Use FFmpeg to convert VOB to preferred format   For lossless
 ffmpeg -i VTS_01_1.VOB -c:a copy -c:v libx265 -preset ultrafast -x265-params lossless=1 ~/mycoolvid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Web Hosting with GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>http://ltratcliff.com/posts/github-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 20:48:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ltratcliff.com/posts/github-io/</guid>
      <description>Github.io Sign up and create a github.io repo/page here: github.io
Custom Domain Purchase a custom domain. I chose google domains Google Domains
Once purchased we need to setup DNS
Google Domains DNS We need to create an A record to point our new domain to the github.io IPs
To get the github.io IPs we can use nslookup
nslookup ltratcliff.github.io There&amp;rsquo;s a handful of IP addresses here, but we are not concerned with the IPV6 ones (2606:50c0:etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glances on SilverBlue after an update</title>
      <link>http://ltratcliff.com/posts/glances_on_silverblue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 19:08:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ltratcliff.com/posts/glances_on_silverblue/</guid>
      <description>Just updated from silverblue 34 to 35 with:
rpm-ostree rebase fedora:fedora/35/x86_64/silverblue The update went very smooth, however there were a few minor caveats.
 My Fedora 34 toolbox was inop Had to add/update to a fedora 35 container created ansible script to make migration easier  --- - hosts: localhost become: true gather_facts: false vars_files: - software.yml tasks: - name: Install software dnf: name: &amp;#34;{{ software }}&amp;#34; state: latest software.yml:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun With Hugo</title>
      <link>http://ltratcliff.com/posts/funwithhugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 13:40:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ltratcliff.com/posts/funwithhugo/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been digging the Hugo static website generator. Getting up and running quickly using github.io pages and Hugo was breeze. Here&amp;rsquo;s a few things I&amp;rsquo;ve learned over the last 2-3 days playing with Hugo
Recommendations This youtube playlist by giraffe academy was a great start. Shout out to Mike Dane for making this content
   Quickstart The Official docs: here help get you setup with installation, and a new project</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offline Go Modules</title>
      <link>http://ltratcliff.com/posts/offline-go-modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 15:11:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ltratcliff.com/posts/offline-go-modules/</guid>
      <description>Using go mod vendor With an existing module  copy go.mod and go.sum files from the offline PC to the internet PC  New module  create a folder on machine with internet access create a go module : go mod init offline  Download dependencies via vendor folder  create a offline_modules.go file :  touch offline_modules.go  add the dependencies you want to download (use _) :  package offline_modules import ( _ &amp;#34;github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>http://ltratcliff.com/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 14:45:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ltratcliff.com/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>About me Born in Miami Florida and raised in Fort Lauderdale. After High-School I went to FSU to study computer science.
After four years of study I left FSU and joined the Marines. In the Marines I worked on electronic equiptment for a SIGINT Battalion.
After the Marines I became a defense contractor and started working as Systems Administrator for an AirForce GEOINT squadron in the AF-DCGS. I did this for 10 years where I worked with some of the smartest people in my career.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
